老公  这绝对是个好主意
Honey, this was such a great idea...
早起点  这样我们就可以独享我们的二人世界了
Getting up early so we can have some quiet time together.
-你这个小混蛋  -你这个大白痴
-You're a jerk! -You're an idiot!
好吧  明早我们稍微再起早点
All right, tomorrow we get up just a little bit earlier.
好了  你们又发什么疯呢
Okay, what's going on, guys?
我受不了了  他哼起来就像只猪
I can't take it anymore! He snorts like a pig.
哼  哼  哼
Oink oink oink!
是吗  你晚上睡觉还会尖叫嘞
Oh yeah?  Well, you scream in your sleep.
好了  够了
All right, enough!
我们要有属于自己的房间
We've got to have our own rooms.
孩子们  我们不谈过这件事了吗
Guys, we've been over this.
-我们的房子没那么多地  -未必
-The house just isn't big enough. -Or is it?
我画了张图表  看  最新就寝规划图
I made a diagram, see? New sleeping arrangements.
老爸老妈睡这  PJ睡这间
Mom and dad go here. P.J. Takes this room.
泰迪这间  我这间
Teddy takes this one and I get this one.
-多完美  -查莉睡哪
-Everybody's happy. -What about charlie?
噢  我忘了说了
Oh, I forgot to mention
在这份计划中
In this plan...
查莉和奶奶一起住
Charlie lives with grandma.
盖比  你能再忍忍吗
Gabe, would you just be patient?
几年后你会有自己的房间的
You're gonna get your own room in a couple of years
等PJ上大...
When P.J. Goes off to coll...
那个  不论PJ上什么
Well, wherever it is that P.J. goes off to.
-噢  嗨  -哦  看看
-Oh hi. -Oh look!
我们的小美女来了
There's our pretty girl.
嘿  你今天终于下床了
Hey, you got out of bed today.
我只是下来拿我的早饭
I just came up to get my breakfast.
宝贝  别拿那个棕色的香蕉  拿黄的
Honey, don't take the brown banana. Get the yellow one.
黄色显得太欢快了
Yellow's too happy a color.
真不敢相信她还为
I can't believe she's still moping about
和斯宾塞分手这件事而郁闷
her breakup with spencer.
事情都过去两天了唉
That was like two whole days ago.
饶了她吧  PJ  斯宾塞可是她的初恋
Give her a break, p.J. Spencer was teddy's first love.
是啊  我是说  你应该能体谅的
Yeah, I mean, you should understand.
毕竟你总是被甩
You get dumped all the time.
-没有  瞎说  -噢  是吗
-No, I don't! -Oh really?
今年你就被亚历克萨给甩了
This year alone you've been dumped by Alexa,
丽贝卡  珍
Rebecca, Jen...
珍  我正和珍约会呢
Jen? I'm dating jen right now.
噢
Oh.
我没告诉你那条留言吗
I didn't give you that message?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast</i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  kenix
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby, </i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好未来
<i>But I know your future is bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There is no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第一季第二十一集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E21 Teddys Broken Hearts Club Band
-好了  大家  我们走了  -你们去哪
-Okay, everybody, we are off. -Where are you going?
我去那个新开的健身房  听说那给免费照看小孩
I joined this great new gym that offers free childcare.
等查莉自己玩的时候  我去健健身
I get to work out while Charlie plays.
太好了  亲爱的
Great, honey.
嘿  盖比  你应该尝尝这个双层糖衣的
Hey, Gabe, you gotta try the double glazed.
知道吗  鲍伯  他们推出买一送一活动
You know, Bob, they're offering a two-for-one special.
挺好的
That's really good to know.
为什么我们只有十二个
Why did we only get a dozen of these?
嗨  达布尼太太  有什么问题吗
Hi, Mrs. Dabney. What's the problem?
-为什么非要有问题  -抱歉  习惯了
-Why would there be a problem? -Sorry, force of habit.
不知道你们有没有人没事做
I was wondering if anyone was available
来帮我把废品搬到车库里
To help me move some junk into my garage.
我来做  十五块一小时
I'll do it! For 15 bucks an hour.
我在想邓肯家
I was thinking of another member
还有没有别人  其他某人
Of the duncan family. Any other member.
抱歉了  我正要去健身房呢
Sorry, but I'm on my way to the gym.
我还有一堆家务活要做
I've got a whole list of chores I gotta do.
看来首项家务活就是“清理甜甜圈盒子”
I see the first thing on that list is "clean out donut box."
十五块一小时  一次  两次
15 an hour, going once. Going twice...
这个小不点怎么样  她看起来挺强壮的
What about that baby? She looks pretty strong.
开工吧
Shall we?
真是纠结...这次我把问题留给我自己了
That's a twist... this time I'm leaving with the problem.
泰迪  出来  俺知道你在里面
Teddy, come on. I know you're in there.
没有  我不在
<i>No, I'm not!</i>
好吧  是你逼俺的
Okay, you're leaving me no choice.
噢
oh!
什么东西死里面了
What died in there?
我的心
My heart.
是吗  我觉着这味道来自你的体外
Yeah, I think the smell is coming from the outside of your body.
你上次洗澡是什么时候了
When's the last time you took a shower?
洗澡也不能冲走我的伤痛
A shower's not going to wash away my pain.
好吧  那我的伤痛怎么办
Okay, how about my pain?
好了  俺要把你带出这阴霾
Come on, we gotta break you out of this funk.
来点音乐如何
How about some music?
算了  我...  我早试过了
No, I... no, I already tried that.
我听些欢快的歌曲  然而我却愈加伤心
I listened to happy songs and they just made me
因为他们是那么的开心
Sad because those people were so happy
而我是那么的伤心
and I'm so sad.
难道你认为
Do you think
就你一人心碎过吗
you're the only person who's ever had their heart broken?
记着当俺和埃米特分手吗
Remember when Emmett and I broke up?
噢  那完全不一样  是你甩的他
Oh, that's completely different. You dumped him.
而且
And...
他是埃米特
He's emmett.
听着  你必须找点事做
Look, you gotta do something.
-哎哟  -赶紧给俺刷牙去
-Ow! -You gotta brush your teeth,
然后梳梳头发
Then brush your hair.
然后再刷刷牙
Then brush your teeth again,
因为  姐们  你的味道太给力了
Because, girl, that breath is nasty!
艾薇  你不能体会我现在的感受
Ivy, you just don't understand what I'm going through.
没有人可以  我男朋友在和我约会的同时
Nobody does. My boyfriend was dating another girl
还在和别的女生约会
At the same time he was dating me.
知道了  要么你重新面对这个世界
Okay. Well, you can either rejoin the world,
要么继续爬回被窝里待上余生
Or crawl back under those covers for the rest of your life
终生痛苦
and be miserable.
谢了
Thank you.
谢你
现在好闻多了
It smells a lot better now.
这还有点箱子
There's some boxes in here too.
哇  这是谁的房间
Whoa, whose room is this?
我儿子罗德尼
My son Rodney.
他现在住在弗罗里达
<i>He lives in Florida now.</i>
他让我自豪让我笑  我心中永远的宝
He's my pride and joy, the love of my life.
达布尼先生怎么样
What about Mr. Dabney?
没错  还是说罗德尼吧
Yep, love that Rodney.
这房间太棒了
This room is so cool.
噢  快看看这床
Oh, check out this bed!
-还会动  -那是水床  你个笨蛋
-It's moving! -It's a waterbed, dummy.
-就像个水上公园  -公园关门了
-It's like a water park. -The park's closed.
快下来
Get off!
现在别给我瞎闹了
Now quit your dilly-dallying
赶紧把那箱子从足球桌上搬下来
and get that box off the foosball table.
足球桌
A foosball table?
这简直就是人间天堂啊
It's like I'm in heaven.
除了你的存在
Except you're here.
好了  跟我走
All right, now come with me.
我们要把一些东西搬出达布尼先生的房间
We have to get some stuff out of Mr. Dabney's room.
你和达布尼先生不住在一起  我爸妈可不这样
You and Mr. Dabney have separate rooms? My mom and dad don't.
你等他们结婚三十周年后再看
Check back with me after their 30th anniversary.
罗德尼  看来你有新室友了
Rodney, looks like you got yourself a roommate.
你磨蹭什么呢
What are you doing?
和罗德尼聊聊天
I'm talking to Rodney.
除了我不许别人和罗德尼聊天  快点
Nobody talks to Rodney but me. Come.
查莉  这位是帕翠莎阿姨
Charlie, this is Patricia.
噢  多可爱的小宝宝啊
Oh, what an adorable child.
她有自己的写真了吗
Has she had her shots?
当然
Of course.
你先和帕翠莎阿姨玩会  然后妈妈我就去
Patricia's going to watch you while mommy
强健体魄  燃烧激情
Pumps the iron, feels the burn,
发挥余热
Treads the mill.
我很高兴听到你这么说
I am so glad to hear you say that.
我们这个健身俱乐部可不欢迎那些
We here at flex appeal frown upon members who join the club
只为了帮忙照顾孩子而入会的会员
Simply for the free childcare.
-有那种人  -还不少呢
-People do that? -Oh yes.
这破事烦死我了  他们甚至不是为了去健身
And it burns my buns. Some of them don't even work out.
他们就这样把孩子扔这
They drop off their kids
然后自己沿着街区去新开的水疗中心进行
and go down the block to the new spa for
按摩和面部护理
massages and facials.
太不像话了  你说沿着街区
That's terrible! Down the block, you say?
好了  我唠叨完了
Well, that's my flex appeal spiel.
-过来吧  查莉  -查莉  去找帕翠莎阿姨
-Come on, Charlie. -Charlie, go to Patricia.
-好了  再见  宝贝  -玩的开心
-All right. Bye, sweetheart. -Enjoy.
-谢谢  我会的  -再见
-Thanks, I will. -Bye.
-拜  宝贝  -我们会很开心的
<i>-Bye, sweetie. -We'll have fun.</i>
即使我们再也见不到对方了
<i>Even if we never see each other again,</i>
我还是会一直爱你的
<i>I'll love you always.</i>
骗子
Liar!
噢  就不能让我消停会吗
Oh, why won't the world just go away?
没想到吧
Surprise.
你又想干嘛
Now what do you want?
好吧  首先你要改变下你这态度
Okay, first of all you can lose the 'tude.
其次  我给你带来了
And second, I brought someone
可以帮你走出阴霾的人
Who will help you out of your funk.
看啊
Ta-da!
-这谁啊  -噢  抱歉
-Who's she? -Oh, sorry.
什么  斯凯勒
What?  Skyler?
你居然给我带了我男友背着我约会的这个女孩
You brought over the girl my boyfriend cheated on me with?
你就是这样帮我的吗
This is how you're helping me?
我以为你说我们要去商场
I thought you said we were going to go over to the mall?
这不是商场
This is so not the mall.
听着  你说过没有人
Look, you said no one
可以体会到你的痛苦  她就可以
Understands what you're going through. She does!
现在你们俩可以相互慰藉了
Now get to healing and whatnot.
你怎么找到她的
How did you find her anyway?
我再问你一遍  斯宾塞
I'm going to ask you again, Spencer.
我要那个女孩的名字和电话号码  现在就要
I want that girl's name and number and I want it now!
我在网上联系到的
I found her on the internet.
我和她没什么说的
I have nothing to say to her.
我和她也没什么说的
And I have nothing to say to her.
听着  你们两个好好谈谈
Look, you two are going to talk it out
把事情解决了  不解决谁也别想走
And make it all better. No one's leaving until then.
-我觉着这什么也解决不了  -我也这么觉着
-I really don't see how this is going to help. -Me either.
太痛苦了
It hurts!
太太太痛苦了
It hurts so bad.
这两个都不怎么好闻
Doesn't smell too good either.
终于离家出走了  是吧
Finally running away from home, huh?
记住  不论你多么想念这个家
Just remember, no matter how homesick you get,
总之不要回来
Just keep going.
我没离家出走  不如说是
I'm not running away. Let's just say
-我找到了属于我的小天地  -没听懂
-I found a place of my own. -What's that supposed to mean?
意思是我现在有房间了  你也有了
It means that I get a room and you get a room.
这就是我要说的
And that's all I'm going to say.
你还是少知道点好
The less you know the better.
是吗  那算你找对人了
Well, then you came to the right guy.
你不会对爸妈说起这件事吗
So you're not going to say anything about this to mom and dad,
是吧
right?
对不起  你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
我已经开始在脑子里构思我的房间了
I was mentally rearranging my room.
好吧  那么
Okay, then,
该说再见了
I guess this is goodbye.
再见了  老弟
So long, little bro.
晚饭时候再见
See you at dinner.
噢  斯宾塞有没有假装打哈欠
Oh, did Spencer ever do that thing where he pretended to yawn
-然后趁机张开双臂搂着你  -没错
-Just so he could put his arm around you? -Yeah!
总是这样
All the time.
嘿  他有没有给你发过“晚安”这类的短信
Hey, did he ever send you those "good night" texts?
有啊  “I.M.Y.”
Yeah. "I.M.Y."?
-这是啥意思  -“我想你”
-What's that supposed to mean? -"I miss you."
原来如此  我还以为是“我做了酸奶”
Oh-hhh! I thought it was "I made yogurt."
是吗  他总谈起酸奶吗
Well, did he talk a lot about yogurt?
从没有  所以我一直想不通
No, never. That's what confused me.
还好你长得好看点
It is a good thing you're pretty.
知道吗  我不得不承认
You know, I have to admit it does kind
把所有事说出来后  感觉好多了
Of feel good to talk all this stuff out.
没错  我不再感觉孤单了
It really does. I don't feel so alone anymore.
“谢谢了  艾薇”
"thank you, Ivy!"
难道没人想说吗
Somebody needed to say it.
噢  知道吗  我以前特郁闷
Oh, you know, I was so upset
然后我就写了一首关于斯宾塞的诗
I actually wrote a poem about Spencer.
是吗  当我郁闷的时候我写了一首关于他的歌
Really? I was so upset I wrote a song about him.
其实  只有旋律
Well, just the music.
我实在想不出...那个...
I couldn't come up with the... The...
往歌里填的叫什么来着
What are those things that you put into songs?
-歌词  -不是
-Lyrics? -No.
就是你要唱的那些字
The words that you sing.
哦天啊  我有个主意
Oh my gosh. I have an idea.
噢  我喜欢那种眼光
Oooh, I like that look in your eye.
我们干吗要这么郁闷
Why should we be miserable
我们干吗不让他郁闷
When we could make him miserable?
艾薇晓得了
Ivy's getting tingly.
我还不晓得
I don't understand what's happening.
我们要报复他
We're gonna get even.
-报复斯宾塞  -晓得了
-With Spencer. -Oh-hhh!
歌词  那东西叫歌词
Lyrics! That's what they're called.
-早啊  老爸  -嗨
-Morning, dad. -Hi.
老天啊  昨天睡得真爽
Oh, man, I had a great night's sleep.
没和你弟弟打架吗
You didn't fight with your brother?
没有  就好像他不在一样
No, it was like he wasn't even there.
我是说  他在
I mean, he was there...
就好像他不在一样
It just felt like he wasn't there.
但他的确在
But he was there.
你对他做了什么
What did you do to him?
没什么  老爸
Nothing. Dad!
多给我一些信任  也许我会成熟的
Give me some credit. Maybe I'm finally growing up.
噢  煎饼  好吃  好吃
Oooh, pancakes! Yummy num num!
早上好大家
Morning, everybody.
你在那摇晃什么呢
Why are you swaying?
可能还不适应在陆地上的生活
Guess I don't have my land legs yet.
-啥  -呃
-What?! -Uh...
我做了个梦  梦见我在一条船上
I had a dream I was on a boat.
这就解释了为啥你昨天在梦里
Which explains why you kept mumbling
一直喊  “喂  老兄”
"ahoy, matey" in your sleep.
（注：海盗的标志性问候语）
别瞎给我帮忙
Don't help me.
好了  女士们
Okay, ladies,
镇压斯宾塞·沃尔什行动  第一条
Spencer Walsh slap down, take one;
音乐来自  斯凯勒
Music by Skyler;
歌词  泰迪
Lyrics by Teddy;
制片人  校对  后期
Produced, rected, choreographed
来自艾薇·勒妮·温茨
By Ivy Renee Wentz.
为啥你就能用全名
How come you get your full name?
因为我是导演
Because I'm the director.
好了  带着对斯宾塞的怒气
Okay, we're feeling angry about Spencer,
预备  开始
On... Action!
我以为他就是真命天子
I thought he was the ideal catch
他说我们就是天生一对
He said we were a perfect match
我认为我们会甜甜蜜蜜
I thought we had a love so sweet
直到我发现他是
Until I found out he was
一个大骗子
A big old cheat!
嘿  大家好吗
Hey, everybody
你们知道吗
Can you dig?
斯宾塞·沃尔什是个两面派
Spencer Walsh is a two-timing pig
一个有着柔情双眼的橄榄球运动员
A football player with big dreamy eyes
从嘴里喷出来的全是谎话
But everything he said turns out to be lies
如果这听起来像是对他的污蔑
Now excuse me if this sounds like a dis
但那个傻瓜都不知道如何亲嘴
But that fool don't even know how to kiss
他即在和她约会  又在和我约会
He was dating her while he was dating me
如今那个废物已成历史
Now that big loser is history
嘿  大家好吗
Hey, everybody
你们知道吗
Can you dig?
斯宾塞·沃尔什是个两面派
Spencer walsh is a two-timing pig!
女士们啊  太完美了
Ladies, that was perfect.
刚才没录上  现在从头再来一遍
Now just one more take and this time I'll hit record.
-这挺不错的嘛  -PJ
-Nice place you got here. -P.J.!
-你怎么找到我的  -我住隔壁
-How'd you find me? -I live next door.
我能看见你
I watched you.
老弟  这里太爽了
Dude, this is awesome.
-这就是传说中的水床吗  -没错
-Is that a waterbed? -Oh yeah.
太好玩了
That was so cool!
-我给你玩次  -好
-Let me do you, ready? -Okay.
尽管来吧
Go for it.
我还以为会更有趣的
I thought that would be more fun.
老弟  这里真不赖
Dude, this is so sweet, man.
这什么都有  水床
You've got everything here... waterbed,
-漫画书  -还有桌上足球
-Comic books... -don't forget foosball.
噢  这简直就是人间天堂
Oh. It's like I'm in heaven.
除了你的存在
Except you're here.
你肯定想问  这里又是哪
And what's in here, you might ask.
我的私人浴室
My own bathroom.
你还有私人浴室
Your own bathroom.
虽然没必要去看
I don't even have to go,
但我还是强迫自己去看看吧
but I'm gonna force myself.
呜
Whoo!
嗨  查莉
Hi, Charlie!
-嘿  宝贝  -练得不错吧
-Hey, baby. -Good workout today?
噢  很好  已经把它推向极限了
Oh, it was great. Really pushed it to the limit.
噢  你在哪把它推向极限了
Oh, where exactly did you push it?
因为我早些时候在健身房没有看到你
Because I was in the workout room earlier and I didn't see you.
因为我在泳池里
Because I was at the pool.
我们没有泳池
We don't have a pool.
我说的那个泳池就在
Okay, I'm talking about the pool of people who are waiting
人们等在阶梯踩踏机什么的旁的那个
By the stair climber thingamajiggy.
知道吗  邓肯夫人
Uh-huh. You know, Mrs. Duncan,
当我在某个词后面加“什么的”时
When I add a "majiggy" to the end of a word
通常意味着我在隐藏什么
It usually means I'm trying to hide something.
-我不知道您在说什么呢  -是吗
-I don't know what you're talking about. -Oh?
如果没什么事了  我还有些
So if you'll excuse me, I'm late for a...
很重要的事什么的要忙
Very important thingamabob.
嘿  艾薇  快给我回电话
Hey, Ivy, call me when you get this.
我刚剪辑完我们的录影带
I just finished editing our music video
而且看起来棒极了
And it looks amazing!
我真想马上传到网上  斯宾塞死定了
I can't wait to upload it. This will ruin Spencer.
噢  是斯凯勒  一会聊
Oh, there's Skyler. Talk to you later.
好了
Okay.
嗨
Hi.
斯宾塞  你来干什么
Spencer, what are you doing here?
-能先进去吗  -我觉着不能
-Can I come in? -I don't think that would be a good idea.
听着  我需要和你谈谈
Look, I need to talk to you.
-没什么好谈的  -有谈的
-There's nothing to say. -Yes, there is.
我想让你知道  这整件事我是多么的对不起你
I want you to know how sorry I am about what happened.
我犯了个大错误
I made a huge mistake.
和斯凯勒约会是我这辈子做过最愚蠢的事情
Hanging out with Skyler was the stupidest thing I've ever done.
泰迪
Teddy,
你才是我的唯一
You're the one I want to be with.
-斯宾塞  我  -听着
-Spencer, I... -look!
我知道我不配
I know I don't deserve it,
但是有什么方法能让你原谅我吗
But is there any way you can forgive me?
我们重新再来可以吗
We can just start over?
不  我做不到
No, I can't.
我已经对你失去信任了
I just don't think I can trust you.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我也是
Me too.
加入这个健身俱乐部
Joining that gym up the street
算是我这辈子的明智之举了
Is the smartest thing I've ever done.
噢  往屁股上再多用点力  我可有四个孩子
Oh, just go a little deeper on the glutes, I've got four kids.
爽啊  就是这
Oh yeah! That's the spot.
噢  那里最难受了
Oh, lots of tension there.
妈妈
Mamama.
嗨  查莉
Hi, Charlie.
查莉
Charlie?!
您的会员资格被取消了
Your membership has been revoked.
嗨
Hi.
-你怎么在这里  -轮到我在这里享受了
-What are you doing here? -I'm taking my turn in the cool room.
-我们又没说要轮流享受  -不  就是要轮流来
-We're not taking turns. -Yes, we are.
-今晚轮到我了  -好吧  反正我不走
-And tonight is my turn. -Well, I'm not leaving.
-好吧  我也不走  -好吧  我也不走
-Well, neither am I. -Well, neither am I.
怎么回事
Well?
对此我不发表任何评论
I have absolutely no explanation for this.
嗨  查莉  好了  嗯
Hi, Charlie. So, um...
我决定不把斯宾塞的视频发到网上了
I decided not to put the Spencer video online.
我是说  不能因为某人伤害了你
I mean, just because somebody hurts you doesn't mean
你就反过来再去伤害他
you need to hurt them back.
那么解决之道就是
So do what I did.
找些朋友来帮你度过难关
Find some friends to help you get through it.
噢  和你小妹唠叨完后
Oh, when we get done talking to your sister,
我们要不要把斯宾塞的视频发到网上
Are we gonna put the spencer video online?
呃  不要  这事我刚刚说过了
Uh, no. That's kind of the whole point of what I just said.
可我没听懂  我是说
I don't get you. I mean,
我是有很多事情搞不懂  但我实在也搞不懂你
I don't get a lot of things, but I really don't get you.
这位就是斯凯勒姐姐  她是不是很漂亮啊
This is Skyler. Isn't she pretty?
祝她好运吧  查莉
Wish her good luck, charlie.
我不管别人说啥
I don't care what anybody says.
没人能把我赶出这间屋子
No one's going to keep me out of this room.
-我也是  -不要
-Or me. -No!
别这样啊  查莉  我们来分享下啊
come-on, Charlie. We can all share!
耶
Yay!
-噢努 德拉格  他可以吗  -噢  噢
-Onoy? Drug? Can he can? -Oh-Oh.
查莉  我知道你在里面
Charlie? I Know You're in-here.
-是你那俩傻哥哥吗  -哥哥
-is Yours fuall-bros? -Bros!